Guide to the Dwight Hall, Yale University, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Records concerning the Board of Trustees, committee meetings and Centennial Campaign Fund, 1969-1993; Accession 2001-A-083
  - Board of Trustees
    - Management Committee (Box 1, Folder 47)
    - Trustees, 1988 October 31 (Box 1, Folder 48)
    - Trustee meeting, 1988 April 11 (Box 1, Folder 49)
    - Advisory Board meeting, 1969 November 10 (Box 1, Folder 50)
    - DH Board of Trustees (notebook) (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Centennial Campaign Fund
    - Pledges received (Box 2, Folder 52)
    - Aetna Foundation (Box 2, Folder 53)
    - Borden Foundation (Box 2, Folder 54)
    - Carolyn Foundation (Box 2, Folder 55)
    - Cudahy Foundation (Box 2, Folder 56)
    - Culpepper Foundation (Box 2, Folder 57)
    - Dana Foundation (Box 2, Folder 58)
    - Hazen Foundation (Box 2, Folder 59)
    - Maguire Foundation (Box 2, Folder 60)
    - Pew Foundation (Box 2, Folder 61)
    - Pine Lenel Foundation (Box 2, Folder 62)
    - SNET (Box 2, Folder 63)
    - 2NDEX (Box 2, Folder 64)
    - Case statement, 1984 June 11 (Box 2, Folder 65)
    - Planned giving (Box 2, Folder 66)
    - Addresses (Box 2, Folder 67)
    - Advocate Press (Box 2, Folder 68)
    - Battell and Chaplancy donors (Box 2, Folder 69)
    - Byers Fund (Box 2, Folder 70)
    - Cabinet (Box 2, Folder 71)
    - 100 Year Anniversary Campaign (Box 2, Folder 72)
    - Campaign final tabulation (Box 2, Folder 73)
    - Campaign/Misc follow-up (Box 2, Folder 74)
    - Campaign plan (Box 2, Folder 75)
    - Campaign pledges (Box 2, Folder 76)
    - Centennial -speeches, 1986 April 11 (Box 2, Folder 77)
    - Centennial Campaign Fund (Box 2, Folder 78)
    - Centennial Campaign Fund steering committee (Box 2, Folder 79)
    - Centennial Committee (Box 2, Folder 80)
    - Centennial Fund (Box 2, Folder 81)
    - Centennial fund checks (Box 2, Folder 82)
    - Centennial Fund givers (Box 2, Folder 83)
    - Centennial Campaign givers/deposits (Box 2, Folder 84)
    - Centennial Planning Committee pre-campaign (Box 2, Folder 85)
    - Centennial reception guests (Box 2, Folder 86)
    - Class info. (Box 2, Folder 87)
    - Class solicitations (Box 2, Folder 88)
    - Consultants search, 1983 December (Box 2, Folder 89)
    - Corporations -New Haven (Box 2, Folder 90)
    - TK Goodale, consultant (Box 2, Folder 91)
    - Interviews -pre-campaign (Box 2, Folder 92)
    - Major gifts committee (Box 2, Folder 93)
    - Major and nucleus (Box 2, Folder 94)
    - Major prospects (Box 2, Folder 95)
    - Objectives (Box 2, Folder 96)
    - Objectives of the campaign (Box 2, Folder 97)
    - Contact sheets (Box 2, Folder 98)
    - Pledges received (Box 2, Folder 99)
    - Prospecting meeting (Box 2, Folder 100)
    - Regional strategy (Box 2, Folder 101)
    - Reunion, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 102)
    - Solicitors' guides (Box 2, Folder 103)
    - Special gift letters (Box 2, Folder 104)
    - Special gifts (Box 2, Folder 105)
    - Photographs (Box 2, Folder 106)
    - Work lists (Box 2, Folder 107)
    - Mayor Dilieto (Box 2, Folder 108)
    - President Giamatti and Schmidt (Box 2, Folder 109)
    - Boston (Box 2, Folder 110)
    - Chicago (Box 2, Folder 111)
    - Denver/Colorado (Box 2, Folder 112)
    - Greenwich (Box 2, Folder 113)
    - Hartford (Box 2, Folder 114)
    - Los Angeles (Box 2, Folder 115)
    - New Haven (Box 2, Folder 116)
    - New York City (Box 2, Folder 117)
    - Philadelphia (Box 2, Folder 118)
    - San Francisco (Box 2, Folder 119)
    - Washington D. (Box 2, Folder 120)
- Dwight Hall congregational student work financial ledger, 1950-1957; Accession 2010-A-062; 0.02; (1 envelope) (Box 1)
- Records, 1951-2017; Accession 2019-A-001
  Restricted until January 1, 2053.
  - Academic mentoring/J2 AMP program, 2005-2006 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Adopt-a-grandparent, 1983-1996 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Agency surveys, 1994-1998 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - AIDS project New Haven, 1989-1999 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Annual reports, 1983-2006 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Bazaar community agency, 2004-2006 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Best buddies-Suzanne Jovin information, 1996-1999 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Board of directors-agendas and packets, 1994-2005 (Box 1, Folder 8-12)
  - Board meetings-reflections module, 2003-2005 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Bone marrow canned food drive, 2001-2002 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Boy Scouts at Dwight Hall, 1982-1992 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Brief history and organizational structure, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Brochures, 1970-2008 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Budgets and financials, 1999-2008 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - By-laws and revision correspondence, 1992-2006 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Campus outreach opportunity league-history and documentation, 1983-1991 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - City Kids Foundation, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Cityscape, 1997-2000 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - City-wide youth coalition, 1993-2000 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Columbus House, 1982-2005 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Community Action by Students Together-correspondence, meetings, agendas and budgets, 1988-2001 (Box 2, Folder 2-4)
  - Community soup kitchen, 1979-1999 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Conflict of interest policy and operation guide, 1987 and 2008 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Connecticut Fund for the Environment, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Connecticut daycare regulations, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Connecituct Voices for Children, 1995-2000 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Connecticut volunteer coordinators, 1984-1986 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Coordinating Council for Children in Crisis, 1983-2000 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, 1991-2001 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Daringly Educational Marvels of Science (DEMOS), 1990-1994 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Diversity Projects, 2004-2005 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Dixwell Q House, 1984-2001 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Dwight Hall Awards, 1990-2017 (Box 2, Folder 16-19)
  - Dwight Hall documents for member groups, 1995-1996 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Dwight Hall Education Network (EDNET), 1997-2000 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Dwight Hall Executive Committee, 1984-2004 (Box 3, Folder 3-7)
  - Dwight Hall hosted programs and events, 1983-2000 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Dwight Hall humanitarian awards, 1985-1993 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Dwight Hall group inventories, 2007-2008 (Box 3, Folder 10-11)
  - Dwight Hall-issues of the "Dwight Hall Hollar" and listserv printouts, 1986-2008 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Dwight Hall Management Fellows-reports, 2005-2008 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Dwight Hall member group inventories, 2002-2008 (Box 3, Folder 14-15)
  - Dwight Hall official guides, 1997-2012 (Box 3, Folder 16-18)
  - Dwight Hall short programs, 1990-2007 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Dwight Hall Summer Internship/Fellowship program-administrative files
    - 1973-1979 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - 1983-1984 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - 1987-1989 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - 1990 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - 1991 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - 1992 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - 1993 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - 1994 (Box 7, Folder 8-9)
    - 1995-1996 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - 1997 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - 1998-1999 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - 2000-2001 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - 2002 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - 2003 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - 2004 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - 2005 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - 2006 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - 2007 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Dwight Hall Summer Internship/Fellowship program-internships by year, 1963-2001 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Dwight Hall staff meeting notes, 1999-2004 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Early childhood education fellows, 1998-2005 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Echoing Green Fellowship, 1995-1999 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Environmental programs and groups, 1997-2001 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Farnam Neighborhood House, 1995-1996 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Elm City Congregation-organized, 1993-2001 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Elm Street move documents, 2008 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Fellowship House, 1982-2001 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Fiscal sponsorship policy, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Fundraising documents, 1999-2010 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Fundraising letters, 1970-1978 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Graduate and Professional Network and volunteer programs, 1985-2001 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Grant applications and correspondence, 1994-2007 (Box 4, Folder 14-15)
  - Group work program leadership handbook, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Herb Cahoon memorial, 2008 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - "I Have a Dream" project, 1990-1995 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - "Influence on Gender on the Structure of Dwight Hall"-report, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Information notebook, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - International programs, 1983-1986 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Judicial volunteer program, 1983-1984 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Jumpstart program, 1994-2007 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Juvenile Justice League, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Lead program brochures, 1991-1995 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Leadership, Education and Athletics in Partnership, 1993-2000 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Leadership Institute, 1997-1999 (Box 4, Folder 27-28)
  - Liability policy and correspondence, 1992-2000 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Literacy programs, 1990-2001 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Magee Fellowship, 1988-2005 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Membership applications, 1991-2007 (Box 5, Folder 2-3)
  - Member group intiatives, 2004-2005 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - NCAA Volunteers for Youth, 1979-1986 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - New Haven Big Brother and Big Sister program, 1980-1999 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - New Haven Boys and Girls Club, 1984-1986 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - New Haven Christian Action Group, 1969-1987 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - New Haven Community Foundation, 1988-1999 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - New Haven Domestic Violence Programs and Services, 1987-1996 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - New Haven Family Alliance, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - New Haven Latino Development Center, 1983-1985 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - New Haven Livable City Center intiative, 1991-2000 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - New Haven Girl Scouts, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - New Haven LULAC, 1984-1986 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - New Haven programs, 1983-2001 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - New Haven programs for children, 1975-2003 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - New Haven rape crisis center, 1985-1992 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - New member correspondence, 1982-1998 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - New program proposals, 1993-2001 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - New Haven religious action groups, 1994-2000 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - New Haven United Way, 1998-2006 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - New Haven Women's Health Services, 1982-1995 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - New Haven YMCA, 1982-1983 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Non-profit career fair, 2004 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Office of New Haven Affairs, 1997-2000 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - One-time projects, 1990-1997 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Open-End Theatre, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Open house ephemera, 1983-2000 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Opening Door program, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Photographs, 1951-2007 (Box 6, Folder 1-5)
  - Programming documents and correspondence, 1990-2001 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Public school interns, 1996-2002 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Reports on poverty in New Haven, 1983-1995 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Religious ministry and religious groups at Yale, 1998-2001 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Resource applications and policies, 1995-2002 (Box 6, Folder 10-12)
  - Resources at Dwight Hall, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - St. Raphael's hospital volunteer program, 1985-1996 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Safety reports and programs, 1990-2000 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Science and Math Achiever Teams, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - School volunteer programs, 1983-1985 (Box 6, Folder 17-19)
  - Service opportunity resources list, 1981-1996 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Social action and social justice education, 2000-2003 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - SPARK/Word Power, 1993-1995 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Splatter! Magazine, 1990-1999 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - State of Connecticut budget cuts, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Student Alliance to Reform Corporations, 1999-2000 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Students for Responsible Investments, 1999-2000 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Student Handbook, 1997-2008 (Box 6, Folder 27-28)
  - Touch Base, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Tutoring in elementary program, 1994-2001 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Transportation policies and correspondence, 1983-1995 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Urban Fellows Program, 1995-2008 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Urban Improvement Corps, 1989-1996 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - U.S. Grant Foundation, 1978-2003 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - U.S. Grand Foundation-annual reports and correspondence, 1978-2003 (Box 8, Folder 7-8)
  - Work-Study correspondence, 1983-1988 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Yale charities drive, 1988-1997 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Yale Club at Dwight Hall, 2001-2002 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Yale College Council-student volunteer surveys, 1980-1995 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Yale daycare programs, 1983-1986 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Yale freshperson conference, 1968-2001 (Box 8, Folder 14-16)
  - Yale Hunger and Homelessness Project, 2003-2010 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Yale instrumental collection, 2000-2002 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Yale Intrafraternity Council, 1986-1993 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Yale-New Haven Hospital, 1981-1992 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Yale Non-Profit Forum, 1996-1999 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Yale President's Public Service Fellowship, 1994-1999 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Yale Red Cross Blood Drive, 1979-1994 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Yale Urban Studies, 1994-1998 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Yale Volunteer Network, 1988-1999 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Youth Bridge, 1992-1994 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Youth Continuum, 1983-1995 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Youth Mentoring Grant Program, 1998-1999 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Youth Together, 1986-1999 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - YWCA Teen Connect Hot-Line, 1985-1987 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Zulu Nation at Yale, 1993-1994 (Box 9, Folder 3)